a massive thing The
last thing I'd say
about ag tech is
a promising sector that
a lot of farmers
The kids don't want
to be farmers anymore
Right so who's going
to do all that
work right We machines
to do it right
Yeah These are conversations
that I've been having
for a time with
families that had farms
and whatever for generation
after generation and their
kids are just leaving
it abandoning the farm
and moving to the
cities And food security
as you mentioned is
the biggest thing that
I've spoken about in
the last few months
Do you also think
though that it's kind
because that sector has
been so stagnant for
so long and so
stuck in its ways
that nobody has gone
over to them previously
and said OK guys
there's a really easy
way that you can
up your game by
doing these certain things
Do think that might
be part of it
I think there are
probably many more